<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">
<book>
<title> Brake Check </title>
<toc/>
<chapter>
<title> Brake Check </title>
<sect1>
<title>
                <emphasis role="bold">General description</emphasis>
            </title>
            <para>Brake Check is a preventive maintenance function. </para>
            <para>This function allows you to perform early detection of potential brake
                failure.</para>
            <para>You can perform brake check by calling the KAREL program BC_SETUP from TP
                program.</para>
</sect1>
<sect1>
<title> Enable/Disable setting </title>
            <para>You can customize enable/disable brake check for each axis.</para>
            <para>If you want to perform brake check on an axis, please set the axis setting to
                “Enable” in Enable/Disable setting screen. Otherwise, please set the axis setting to
                “Disable”. On robot axes, the default setting is “Enable”. On an axis other than
                robot axes (aux axis, servo gun, or etc.), the default setting is “Disable”.</para>
</sect1>
        <sect1>
            <title>Brake Torque Setting</title>
            <para>This function needs the specification value of brake torque for each axis in order
                to determine the torque that is to be commanded during brake check. </para>
            <para>On robot axes, the brake torques have been set automatically, however, on an axis
                other than robot axes (aux axis, servo gun, or etc.), brake torque is not set
                automatically, so please manually set the brake torque if you need brake check on
                such an axis. For the specification value of brake torque, please refer to “BRAKE
                SPECIFICATIONS” on the corresponding AC SERVO MOTOR DESCRIPTIONS.</para>
        </sect1>
</chapter>
</book>
